

MILENE TOAZZA

Front-end Developer

- Porto Alegre
- mihtoa.github.io
- **%** +55 51 99763 3192
- @ @mihtoa
 - mitoe@live.com

about me

Hello there! How are you? ;D So, I'm a Front-end Developer about 3 years. Recently I'm working with ecommerce front-end development. My study focus in this time have been JavaScript. If you want we can talk to know better me, it'd be a pleasure!



EDUCATION

2018-2020 | Udemy, edX, Udacity

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

Self-taught study on topics like JavaScript, React, Modern CSS, tests and others.

2013-2017 | UniRitter

PUBLICIDADE E PROPAGANDA

Bacharelado em Comunicação Social.

skills

Schell script JavaScript

React HTML Git
CSS Sass jQuery

Node.js Gulp Webpack

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present | Vnda Ecommerce

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Front-end development of e-commerce projects.

Git - GitLab - Liquid - HTML - CSS - Sass - Gulp JavaScript - Node.js - jQuery - Schell script

2018 | Reweb

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Front-end development and maintenance of automotive sites. HTML - CSS - JavaScript - jQuery - Twig

2016 - 2018 | Bublitz.ag

ART DIRECTOR

Art director exercising activities related to: visual identity, web design and marketing digital.